Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Gail Perry - Learning Institute Early Childhood Education, Undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Appeals (Including EEO Cases), 1970-1976 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - Application - Misc., 1976 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Personnel, 1973-1975 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Personnel - Experts and Consultants, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Personnel - Independent D.C System, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Personnel - General Policies etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - General Policies etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1976 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Personnel- Labor Relations, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Position Classification, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Position Control, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Personnel: Principal Selection (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Personnel: Principal Selection (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Personnel 8 Qual. Standards, 1972-1977 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Regional Supt. Selection, 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - Teacher Assignments, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - Teacher Selection - Local, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Tenure Problmes (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Tenure Problmes (Folder 2 of 2), 1973 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Tenure: Carter vs Barry, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - Vacancy Notices, 1974-1977 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Personnel - Vacacy Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Petworth School, 1972-1976 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Phillips, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Reuben Pierce, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Planning Research and Evaluation, Undated (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Poems, 1972-1975 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Police (Office Friendly etc. ), 1972-1974 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Polls, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Postage, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Powell School (principalship), 1973-1978 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Pregnant Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Price Water House Study, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Prince George's County, 1975-1977 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Principal Evaluations, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Principals - Small Schools, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Priority Goals, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Procurement - Minority Enterprises, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Project Open, 1973-1976 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Delores Pryde, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Proposals, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Public Information Office Communications, 1973-1976 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Publications, 1972-1976 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Pupil Membership - Oct 21 1971 By Schools By Grades and By Race Same - Mar 2 1972 and following years (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Pupil Membership - Oct 21 1971 By Schools By Grades and By Race Same - Mar 2 1972 and following years (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Pupil Membership - Oct 21 1971 By Schools By Grades and By Race Same - Mar 2 1972 and following years (Folder 3 of 3), 1972-1974 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Pupil Membership Oct 21 1971 (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Pupil Membership Oct 21 1971 (Folder 2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Pupil Membership Projection, 1972-1976 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Pupil Personal Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Pupil Teacher Ratio Class Size etc., 1972-1979 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Pupil Personnel Services, 1972-1976 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Operation "Push", 1976 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Quality Education etc. Letters from Parents to M. Barry, 1972-1973 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Rabaut, 1975-1976 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Rabaut Jr. High, 1972-1975 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Racism - Nat Student Conference, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Randell Jr. High School, 1974-1977 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Randle Highlands - elem. School, Undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Rap, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Ravenswood Calif City School Dist., 1968-1972 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Raymond School, 1974-1976 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Reading: Cureton Plan (Sent by Nelson S. Burke), 1972 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Read: Right to (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Read: Right to (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Read: Right to (Folder 3 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Right to Read Proposal, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Reading is Fundamental (RIF), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Recreation Dept., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Red Cross, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Reduction- In- Force (Inc. Swaim Letters), 1972-1976 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Region I, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Region II (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Region II (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Region III (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Region III (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Region IV, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Region V, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Region VI (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Region VI (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Regional Locator, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Regional Supt., 1974-1977 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Gwen Reiss, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Religion - Establishment Cause, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Reorganization - Central Adm (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization - Central Adm (Folder 2 of 2), 1974 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Relocation Programs DCRLA- etc., 1971 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Reorganization and Decentrization, 1972-1973 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Research and Evaluation, 1972-1975 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Assn for Retarded Children Inc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Assn for Retarded Children Inc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Retirement, 1977-1980 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Retirement (Mcl Disc. Serve. Annuities, 1976-1978 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Hermoine Rhones (Whitter School), 1972 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Alaire Rieffel, 1978-1980 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - River Terrace School, 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Paul Robeson, 1976-1977 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Theo Roosevelt High School (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Theo. Roosevelt High School (Folder 1 of 2), 1973 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Rosemary Hills School (Montgomery College), 1972-1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Rosenfield A.A Memos, 1972-1975 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Ross School, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Rudolph School, 1973-1977 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Rules '77- (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Rules Jan '77, 1976-1977 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Rules etc. July 1975- Dec '76 (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Rules etc. July 1975- Dec '76 (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Rules etc. July 1975- Dec '76 (Folder 3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Rules etc. Dec 1974 - June 1975 (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Rules etc. Dec 1974 - June 1975 (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Rules etc. Sept- Nov. 1974 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Rules etc. July-Aug 1974 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Rules etc. Jan 1974- June 1974 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Rules etc Calender Year 1973 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Rules etc Calender Year 1973 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Rules including suspension/dress codes etc. thru Dec 1972(Folder 1 of 2), 1973 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Rules including suspension/dress codes etc. thru Dec 1972(Folder 1 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Rules/Personnel/Chap X etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Rules/Personnel/Chap X etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1975 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Rules 1870, 1870-1974 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Rules - Corporal Punishment, 1973-1975 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Rules: Polls/Special Meetings etc., 1973-1976 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Rules CPE and Legislation in General - 1973-1976 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Rules CPE and Legislation in General - 1973-1976 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Rules 'CPE B Legislation in General - 1973-76 II (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Rules 'CPE B Legislation in General - 1973-76 II (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Rules 'CPE B Legislation in General - 1973-76 II (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Rules 'CPE B Legislation in General - 1973-76 II (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Rules 'CPE B Legislation in General - 1973-76 II (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Safety/Drugs etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Safety/Drugs etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1976 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Salary Legislation etc. (Folder 1 of 3), 1972-1984 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Salary Legislation etc. (Folder 2 of 3), 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Salary Legislation etc. (Folder 3 of 3), 1972 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Salary Payment Problems, 1974-1977 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Saturday College, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Savoy School, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Gretchen Schafft, 1976 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships - Fellowships, 1972-1976 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - School Without Walls, 1972-1976 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - School - Community Relations, Undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Schwartz, 1975-1978 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Science (Folder 1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Science (Folder 2 of 3), 1976 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Science (Folder 3 of 3), 1972-1976 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Scott - Montgomery, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Scott's Son - TRF to LaFayette, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Secondary Education School Eval., 1972 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Secondary- Post Secondary Twelve Teen Project, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Secondary Schools Course Descriptions (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1976 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Secondary Schools Course Descriptions (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Secretarial and Clerical Unit, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Security (Stolen Equipment etc.), 1973 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Seed, 1970-1971 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Self - Government, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Jack Sessions, 1972-1974 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Sevice Area Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Sexism and Sex (Folder 1 of 2 ), 1973-1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Sexism and Sex (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Shaed School, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Frank Schaffer Corona, 1978-1980 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Sharpe Health School, 1972-1977 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Shaw Report, 1971-1976 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Shepherd PTA etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Shepherd PTA etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Shoes and Clothing for Children, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Lett Simmons, 1974-1976 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Size School Complex, 1974-1977 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Barbara A. Sizemore (Folder 1 of 2), 1975 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Barbara A. Sizemore (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Conrad P. Smith, 1976 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Frank Smith, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Smoking, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Solar Heat, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - S.W Ed. Task Force, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Special Education Infromation Center for Handicapped Children, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Special Education (General) Thru Dec 31 1972 (Folder 1 of 3), 1972-1980 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Special Education (General) Thru Dec 31 1972 (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Special Education (General) Thru Dec 31 1972 (Folder 3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Special Education Budget Problems, 1973-1975 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Special Education (Ed. Comm. Of the States), 1972-1974 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Special Edu. (General) Calender Year, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Special Education - General - 1974-1976 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Special Education - General - 1974-1976 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Special Education - General - 1977 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Special Education - Advisory Panel, 1976 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Specail Education - Associate Sup't Position, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Special Education History - Lindo, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Special Education - Rieffal Rep't, 1972-1980 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Special Education Goals, 1973-1975 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Special Education Transportation (Folder 1 of 2), 1980 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Special Education Transportation (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Special Edu. (Tuition Grants) (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Special Edu. (Tuition Grants) (Folder 2 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Special Edu. (Tuition/Grants etc. Particular Students) (Folder 1 of 3), 1973-1977 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Special Edu. (Tuition/Grants etc. Particular Students) (Folder 2 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Special Edu. (Tuition/Grants etc. Particular Students) (Folder 3 of 3), 1972 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Special Edu. (Connecticut), 1972-1973 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Special Ed. (Kentucky Task Force), 1971 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Special Eduucation Massachussetts, 1972-1975 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Special Education - New York, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Speech and Hearing, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Spingarn Instructional Unit, 1973-1978 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Staff Development (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Staff Development (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Staff Development Center for Educational Advancement, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Staff Development International Development Program, 1971-1974 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Staff Development Open Space Schools, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - State boards oped. Ass'n of, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - State Boards of Education, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - State Board Functions, 1972-1974 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - State/County/Municipal Empl.AFL CIO, 1976-1978 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Stevens School, 1972-1979 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Stick Up for Breakfast, 1975-1978 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Stuart Jr. High School, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Student Advisory Council - Ad Hoc, 1972-1976 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Student Affiars Office, 1972-1976 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Student Loan Progrm and Grant Programs, 1972-1979 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Student Serving Community Invoc. Committeee (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Student Serving Community Invoc. Committeee (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Substitute Teachers - Notes of, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Substitute Teaching by Administrators, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Summer School (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1978 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Summer School (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1978 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Summer, Undated (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent - Acting, 1973-1976 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent Appt V.E Reed, 1973-1977 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Superintendents Circulars etc., 1972-1976 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Superintendent - Contract of Employment, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent Election Bill etc., 1972 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Superintendents Inaguaration, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Supt's Out- of- city Trips Leave etc, 1974-1975 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum of understanding with Superintendent, 1972-1975 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Superintendants' 120 day report, 1971-1975 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Superintendants Report, 1971-1976 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Superintendent's Role (Howard Univ. Students), 1973 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Superintendents' Salaries etc, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Superintendent - Search Com etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Superintendent - Search Com etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1973 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Superintendent Search Brochures, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent's Staff Directory, Undated (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Supervision and Intrusion (Elementary), 1972 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Supply Requisitions etc., 1976 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Suspension Costs, 1972-1973 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Swaim, 1972-1974 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Takoma School (Folder 1 of 2), 1967-1977 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Takoma School (Folder 2 of 2), 1967-1977 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Taxes and Revenue, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Mattie G. Taylor, 1974-1975 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Pat Taylor Proposal, Undated (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Teacher Corps - Portal Schools, 1973-1976 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - DC et al V Wash. Teachers U (Folder 1 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - DC et al V Wash. Teachers U (Folder 1 of 4), 1976 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - DC et al V Wash. Teachers U (Folder 1 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - DC et al V Wash. Teachers U (Folder 1 of 4), 1972 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Teachers Union (W.H Simmons) (Folder 1 of 3), 1974-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Union (W.H Simmons) (Folder 2 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Union (W.H Simmons) (Folder 3 of 3), 1973 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Teachers Union Negotiations -1974 (Folder 1 of 4), 1974-1979 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Union Negotiations -1974 (Folder 2 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Union Negotiations -1974 (Folder 3 of 4), Undated (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Teachers Union Negotiations -1974 (Folder 4 of 4), Undated (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Union Negotiated - 1975 (Folder 1 of 5), 1976-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Union Negotiated - 1975 (Folder 1 of 5), 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Union Negotiated - 1975 (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Teachers Union Negotiated - 1975 (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Union Negotiated - 1975 (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Union (Strike) (Folder 1 of 3), 1972-1973 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Teacher's Union (Strike) (Folder 2 of 3), 1972 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Teacher's Union (Strike) (Folder 3 of 3), 1972 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Teamsters Union, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Survey, 1972-1976 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Testing - 10176 - (Policy etc.) (Folder 1 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Testing - 10176 - (Policy etc.) (Folder 2 of 4), 1976 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Testing - 10176 - (Policy etc.) (Folder 3 of 4), 1976 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Testing - 10176 - (Policy etc.) (Folder 4 of 4), 1976 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Test Results - Test etc. (1 of 4), 1975-1979 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Test Results - Test etc. (2 of 4), 1972-1976 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Test Results - Test etc. (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Test Results - Test etc. (4 of 4), 1971-1972 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Textbook Committee, 1969-1976 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Thanks and Thank You Messages!, 1975-1977 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Transcental Meditation - TM, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Tirana Letters and Memos, 1971-1972 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Transfer and Assignments (Students), 1973-1976 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Transfer of Teachers - Policy, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Travel to Conventions etc., 1972-1978 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - William Treanori, 1974-1976 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Trinity College, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Tri-School, 1972-1976 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Truancy and Dropout Prevention, 1972-1977 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Trues Dell School, 1972-1977 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Trust Funds, 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Tubman School, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Tuition Exemptions and Rates (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1977 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Tuition Exemptions and Rates (Folder 2 of 2), 1947-1973 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Joseph Turner and M. Raskin, 1977 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Turner School, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - TWC- Congress (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1979 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - TWC- Congress (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Typewriters, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - United Black Funds, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - University Higher Education, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Update, 1972 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Urban Coalition - J.W Smith Etc., 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Urban Food Proj., 1976 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Urban League - Street Academy etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Urban League - Street Academy etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1976 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Urban Service Corps, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Upward Bound, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Merle G. Van Dyke, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Vandalism - Violence, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - John Vasconcellos, 1973-1976 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Carlton W. Veazey (City Council), 1972 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Vendors - Licensed, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Training, 1972-1976 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Video Cassette Demonstration Proposal, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Vocational Education (Folder 1 of 4), 1977 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Vocational Education (Folder 2 of 4), 1976-1978 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Vocational Education (Folder 3 of 4), 1974-1976 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Vocational Education (Folder 4 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Voc-Ed- Career Dev (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1978 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Voc-Ed- Career Dev (Folder 2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Voc. Ed., 1972-1973 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Exploration of Health Careers, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Voc. Ed. - D.C Advisory Council (Folder 1 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Voc. Ed. - D.C Advisory Council (Folder 1 of 3), 1972-1976 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Voc. Ed. - D.C Advisory Council (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Vocational Ed. Foundation (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Vocational Ed. Foundation (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Voter Registration etc, 1972-1976 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - WETA-TV, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - WAMATA (Metro), 1976 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Walker - Jones, 1972-1973 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Jeanne Walton, 1972 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Ward I Profile, 1975-1977 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Ward 2 Profile etc., 1975-1977 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Ward 3 Profile; etc, 1972-1976 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Ward 4 School Questionaires, 1974-1975 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Ward IV Council - Attendance Old Mailing List, Undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Ward Meeting - 1973-1976 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Ward 4- Profile etc., 1975-1977 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Ward V, 1974-1977 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Ward IV, 1976-1977 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Ward VII Vacancy, 1973 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Ward VII Profile, 1976-1978 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Ward 8 Data for Meetings, 1974-1977 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Ward Distribution of Schools, 1972-1976 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Wards of DC, 1973 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - John E. Warren, 1975-1977 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Wash. Center for Metro Studies, 1971-1975 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Washington Evie., 1972-1974 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Coash. Hishlands Comm. School Raj, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Washington, 1971-1972 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Wash. Tectlinical Institute, 1972 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Washington Mini-School Corporation, 1972-1975 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - M.M Washington Vocational School, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Weather (Closns School), 1972-1977 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Weatherless, 1974 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - West School Construction, 1973-1976 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - West School Plans, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Webster School, 1970-1974 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Western High School of the Arts (Folder 1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Western High School of the Arts (Folder 2 of 3), 1974-1976 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Western High School of the Arts (Folder 3 of 3), 1975 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Arts H.S/Shaw, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Duke Ellington School of the Arts, 1976 (Box 149, Folder 2)